https://www.brideofchristrobes.com/our-privacy-statement

Our Privacy StatementBride of Christ Robes has created this Internet privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to user privacy. Bride of Christ Robes believes that consideration for our customer's privacy is the basis for sound business practices. This statement is intended to apply to all visitors of web sites owned and operated by Bride of Christ Robes. If you have any questions after reading this privacy statement, you may contact us at Info@BridesofChristRobes.com
Collection of Information
Bride of Christ Robes does not collect personal information about visitors except when visitors specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis. For example, such personally identifiable information may be gathered from the registration process for subscription sites or services and in connection with content submissions, community postings (e.g., chat and bulletin boards), suggestions, and transactional areas. Such information may be used by Bride of Christ Robes for the following purposes: contacting a subscriber regarding account status, changes to the subscriber agreement, special discounts, promotions, products offered and other matters relevant to the underlying service and/or the information collected. Visitors and customers should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose personal information (e.g., user name, e-mail address) on the feedback areas of Bride of Christ Robes website, that information, along with any information disclosed in the visitor's communication, can be collected, and correlated but will not be used by or distributed to third parties.
Thank you,
Bride of Christ Robes Management Staff
